

JENNIFER CORANGUEZ

jennifer.coranguez@gmail.com | (480) 617-5925 | Chandler, AZ 85225

LINKS

- www.linkedin.com/in/jennifercoranguez
- https://github.com/Jennycoranguez

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Well-qualified Full Stack Developer familiar with a wide range of programming utilities and languages. Knowledgeable of backend and frontend development requirements. Handles any part of the process with ease. Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities offering 3 years of related experience.

SKILLS

- HTML / CSS
- GIT
- JavaScript
- Third-party API's, AJAX / JSON
- Node.js
- Object-oriented programming (OOP)
- Express.js servers
- MySQL
- Object-relational mapper, ORM (Sequelize)

- Model-view-controller (MVC) framework (Handlebars.js)
- United testing
- Agile methodology
- Heroku
- Computer science
- MongoDB and NoSQL
- Progressive web apps (PWAs)
- React
- MERN

WORK HISTORY

Business Owner | Flowers In Paris - Chandler, AZ

03/2022 - CURRENT

- Devised and deployed sales and marketing tactics to drive strategic growth and support achievement of revenue goals.
- Put together realistic budgets based upon costs and fees for successfully operating business.
- Worked with marketing teams to create print and online advertisements to bring in new customers.
- Studied market to determine optimal pricing of goods and capitalize on emerging opportunities.

Volunteer Front Desk | HonorHealth - Scottsdale, AZ 07/2020 - 12/2021

- Welcomed customers with friendly greeting, answered general questions, gathered nature of visit and directed to specific offices.
- Balanced employee availability, customer schedules and maximum

- load levels when scheduling appointments.
- Answered questions and addressed, resolved or escalated issues to management personnel to satisfy customers.

Driver | Doordash - Chandler, United States

12/2018 - 12/2021

- As a driver i would use my phone and vehicle to accept and deliver food orders.
- As driver we pick food up from restaurants or convenience stores and deliver it to the customer at a set location.
- We make our own schedule.
- I would always make sure environment was clean before picking up food and dropping it off at a customer house.
- I would always have great customer service with the customers.

Gymnast Coach | Scottsdale Gymnastics And Trampoline - Scottsdale, AZ

02/2018 - 05/2019

- Practiced with team on schedule and trained alone to enhance athletic abilities and contributions to team success.
- Monitored competitor activities to assess strategies and gain advantages in future matches.
- Attended all practices, meetings and workouts on time.
- Worked with coaches and trainers to understand and implement improvement strategies.

EDUCATION

University of Arizona, Tucson, AZ

08/2022

Certification: Full Stack Developer

Saguaro High School, Scottsdale, AZ

05/2019

High School Diploma